[The following events are a work of fiction.
The characters' names, behaviors, and actions
are not related to any institution,
organization, or profession, and are created
for entertainment purposes only.
Viewer discretion is advised]
Ouch, that stings.
It's going to hurt a bit.
How's the inmate?
She passed out
and only sustained minor knee injuries.
I see.
There's one more thing.
She has Alzheimer's.
Are you sure?
I've performed an initial assessment,
and it's clear she has Alzheimer's.
I'll see what I can do about it.
Please do.
Right.
Are you badly hurt, Pa?
I'm okay, love.
It was careless of me.
The 3D gang did this to you, right?
It was an accident.
Nobody was to blame.
Here's the photo.
Thank you, love.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, love.
I'm okay.
I'll be fine soon.
Hey.
Mangpor's business
is doing so much better.
Are you concerned about this?
Do you want me to tell her to pull back?
No need to do that.
The more sales she makes, the better.
We simply have to increase the cut.
No problem. I'll look into that.
By the way...
I need your help.
What is it?
Well...
Can you keep an eye on Claire?
I'm worried she'll have
her revenge on Deedee and Duen.
Do your sisters
want to get their sentences reduced?
They always cause trouble.
Dao.
You've got to make sure they behave.
Don't make me change my mind
about their requests,
or no one will be able to
take care of your mother
and your son.
Hey.
Remember this.
If I didn't adore you,
you wouldn't get to live
this comfortably.
You know that, right?
How can an inmate enter this room?
I called her myself.
Is something urgent?
I need to discuss something private.
You may leave.
Understood.
Dad.
You told me a male guard
always has to be with a female one,
so what was that about?
The female inmate Dao
is the head of the inmates.
She was just here
to give me a general report.
So what's the matter?
In the evening, in the leisure room,
inmate Duen pushed inmate Porn,
causing her to pass out.
Inmate Dao already reported that to me,
stating it was an accident.
I heard there was a fight
before the assault
- and...
- What you heard
is different from what I've heard.
Inmate Dao said that
inmate Duen didn't mean to push her.
Even though inmate Dao was a witness,
inmate Duen really pushed inmate Porn,
who has Alzheimer's.
She requires better treatment
for her condition in a hospital.
Okay. That's enough.
As for the issue between
those three inmates,
I've had enough.
Right now, you need to leave.
Understood.
Oh, my goodness!
Deedee, where are you going?
Taking a shower.
I'm so fucking annoyed.
I'm gonna take a shower to feel better.
But Dao told us not to go anywhere.
You're not letting me relieve myself?
Ever since I was born,
Dao's never slapped me in the face.
I don't get why she's afraid
of that Rabid Dog.
Don't you remember
how many inmates
she sent to the hospital?
Duen...
Don't tell me that
you're also scared of her.
Honestly, I think
she's way below your league.
She's simply insane,
not that good or anything.
One more.
Oh, my...
I told you not to let anyone in.
Rabid Dog...
Don't be so scared.
Or else it won't be fun.
Who told you I'm scared of you?
That's great, then.
Karakade and Mathusorn,
where did you go?
Come and help us!
Don't...
Hey! Let me go!
Stop it!
You're actually trying to kill us?
Stop!
Stop it! I give up!
I give up.
Let go of my sis.
I gave up.
Don't mess with my company again.
Duen...
You need to have
her confession invalidated.
How can I do that?
The court has rendered its verdict.
You put an innocent person behind bars.
Aren't you feeling anything?
Why didn't you raise an objection
during the announcement?
Can you stop getting on my nerves?
You were there.
You knew he forced me.
I had no choice.
Top,
I had no choice, either.
I did it for your own good,
as your father demanded.
Hey!
Who is stealing my car?
Hey! Where the fuck
are you taking my car?
What a speed demon.
I sold it.
How could you?
How am I supposed to get around now?
That's your problem,
not mine.
If you want to get around,
just hail a cab.
You're not going to visit
your girlfriend in prison, are you?
You're so dense,
you don't get anything.
Fine. I'll tell you this.
Our main policy
for running the campaign is
to eradicate drug use.
And your girlfriend
got arrested on such charges...
Bell didn't do it.
Who cares if she did it or not?
Just going to the prison
will make the headlines.
Delete all of her photos.
Make sure they can't trace back to you.
Got it?
What?
You're mad at me?
You want to punch me, huh?
Go ahead. Do it.
Here.
If you punch me right now,
I might see
the man in you.
Delete the photos.
Make sure nothing
can be traced back to us.
Sorry, the number...
Hello, Auay.
I can't contact Top.
Have you been keeping in touch with him?
Since your incident occurred,
I haven't seen him at all.
How's father?
I'm not on duty anymore.
Top stopped hiring me some time ago.
What?
Then who's in charge?
I do not know.
[Reintegrating good citizens into society]
Come on! Let's go!
- Hey!
- Hey! Move it!
What happened to you?
You're bleeding.
I ran into a cell door.
How's Pa'Porn?
She's alright.
What about you?
What's wrong?
Why do you look so down?
Oh...
Something threw me off earlier,
but I'm fine now.
Better now?
Your nose, I mean.
Oh...
It'll get better.
Thank you.
Take the meds, okay?
Then, you can sleep.
All good?
Open your mouth.
Alright.
You're amazing, like always.
Why are you sleeping so early tonight?
Are you a young girl or something?
Tomorrow is
the family visit day, isn't it?
My son...
He's coming to see me.
Then rest well, okay?
Thank you, love.
Since I was born,
I've never had ill will towards anyone.
Just being thrown in prison
is bad enough.
Is it too much to ask
for just one good thing?
A pair of size 38 shoes, please.
Out of stock.
What about the one behind you?
Can't you just have a look at it for me?
Size 38 shoes.
I told you we're out of stock.
Oh, Bell?
Where are your shoes?
I stopped by the Buddha room,
and then they were gone.
Just go and get a new pair.
It won't cost much.
I've already been there,
but it was sold out.
Sold out?
Mm.
Oh, I forgot.
The general shop
is run by Deedee's company.
Well...
After I'm done working,
I'll get you a pair, okay?
Thank you.
I'll repay you as soon as I can.
Don't mention it. It's nothing.
I think
we have to find a way to make them
stop messing with you,
or else you won't make it.
I'll help you, okay?
Please don't.
You might get dragged into this.
Just knowing you want to help me
means a lot to me.
How far did you walk here barefoot?
Just look at my feet.
Do we know each other?
Pa, my name is Claire.
You're waiting for your son, right?
He said he'd be a bit late,
so he wanted me to take you
for a stroll in the meantime.
Please go for a stroll with me.
Oh...
What is this room, love?
It's a storage room.
There's a Buddha image, too.
I want to pray for a bit.
Let me pray first, okay?
(Chanting)
Claire?
Has my son died?
I remember now, love.
When his funeral was held,
I was praying, just like this.
Someone hurt him
and took his life.
So I ran over the perpetrator.
That...
That's why I ended up here?
- May I share the bed with you?
- Sure.
Why are you so kind to me, love?
When I first arrived here,
you were the only person
who took care of me
and even taught me gardening.
So, are you good at it now?
Why?
I didn't keep at it consistently.
My instructor is forgetful...
I'm sorry, love.
Why are you waking up so early, Pa?
I'm going for a walk to get some exercise.
You...
Please take care of the plants, okay?
No worries, Pa.
I'll take care of them.
Hey.
Your business is doing well, huh?
Oh, sis...
Where did you get the news?
It's only doing alright.
Oh.
Is that so?
My sales have dropped
because inmates
are buying from you, huh?
Oh, well...
If my sales are high,
you'll get your cut too, right?
I think my cut
should be increased, right?
Increased?
The 30% cut
is already a lot.
You've been selling more.
You're selling your stuff on our turf.
That means it should be
a 50-50 split, right?
Oh, come on.
I've got initial costs to pay as well.
How about a 60-40 split?
If I raise the prices,
no one's going to buy my stuff.
If that's the case,
we'll both earn nothing.
If we can't settle on a 50-50 split,
you're out of business.
That's a yes if you're taking this long.
Let's go.
Wait!
I'll make it a 50-50 split.
Don't be late with the payment.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry. I just wanted to help.
Stay out of this.
Why aren't they sprouting buds?
I can step in now, can't I?
Roses prefer rich,
well-drained loamy soil.
They grow well in sunny spots.
The sunnier, the better.
So we have to move them, right?
The first step is to change the soil.
We might as well move them
while we're at it.
Where are the garden trowels
and shovels?
I'll go get them.
Just put them there.
Over there.
Yeah, right there.
Here it is.
You're off to a good start.
If we help tend the roses,
they'll grow and flourish, I'm sure.
Trust me.
Right?
Mm.
I guess.
Oh, hello!
How are you doing, love?
- Hello, Pa.
- Hi.
How are you?
- I'm doing great.
- That's lovely.
Pa, how are you?
I'm doing well, love.
- Please be careful while walking.
- Thank you.
Outside?
Right.
- Hello, Pa'Porn.
- Oh, hello, love.
- What are you doing?
- Hello.
- We're tidying up the lawn.
- Oh, I see.
- The weather's nice today.
- Yes, love.
You're gorgeous!
You're the most beautiful of all!
Go back where you came from
right now, Kae.
Girls, I've got to talk to you.
But we have nothing
to talk about with you.
I have a way for you
to gain more money
and power than Wichai.
That's garbage.
Are you pulling my leg or what?
I'm serious.
Do you want to know?
What is it?
Loan money to inmates.
I'm the moneylender,
and you bring us clients.
Then the profits are split 50-50.
Loan money?
Who are we going to lend money to?
Ridiculous.
The inmates, of course.
They need money to buy stuff.
If they take a loan from us,
the interest is yours.
This will make you rich in no time.
With that wealth comes power.
Everyone will have to respect you,
even Wichai.
We'll check with Dao first.
If you do that, he'll find out about this.
Then he'll ask for a cut,
just like he did with Mangpor's business.
Trust me.
We can run this business by ourselves.
It's just Deedee,
Duen,
- Karakade,
- Oh?!
and Mathusorn.
You just find and convince our clients.
I'll lend them money.
Simple as that.
What do you want...
out of this?
Just get your hands off Bell
and part ways.
That's all I ask.
Gosh.
Why's everyone backing that girl?
Why do I have to adhere to your plan?
Take the money and get even with Bell,
sounds much better, doesn't it?
If you lay a hand on Bell,
you won't get any money from me.
As for this plan to loan money,
I'll propose it to the others instead.
Oh...
Think carefully
about the offer.
Help me get power first,
and we'll talk about this later.
Sure.
Just wait and see.
Consider the plan.
Interesting, isn't it?
Yeah!
- Sis!
- Hey!
You should consider her offer.
It does sound great.
♫Who wants to be a millionaire?♫
♫Me, of course!♫
Sis, let me take care of this.
- Go, go, go!
- Sure!
Shit! Kae!
Why were you so quiet?
You scared me!
Hey, Deedee's offering loans
at a 20 percent interest rate.
Are you interested?
20 percent?
Gosh, that's too much.
That's a no for me.
I'm here to talk business.
Enough of this.
I'm done splitting cuts with people.
I'm not here to ask for a cut.
I'm here to ask you
to be my business partner.
Sister.
Want to get a loan?
Why do I need that much money here?
I'm loaning money.
Once the inmates have money,
they'll order stuff from you.
In return, this gives you more clients.
What about you? Are you interested?
No, I don't want to be in debt.
What do I have to do?
Sell your entire stock
to me.
No inmates want to take a loan.
Do you know the concept
of demand and supply?
We stayed quiet 'cause we don't know.
Damn, just explain it!
Let me illustrate.
It's simple.
Demand is a desire to purchase.
Supply is the goods we have.
We have to make them want our supplies
so much that they'll take out loans
to buy what they want.
If people really want our supplies,
we can charge whatever we want.
Stand in line, please!
Now, we can just sit back
and earn our profit.
It's basically killing two birds
with one stone.
- Give me one!
- I'll take two.
20 percent, okay?
All done.
Whose is this?
I got it for you.
You didn't have any the other day.
Whoa.
I'm actually craving this.
Thank you.
What's gotten into you?
I've got good news.
I...
I've cleared things up
with Deedee for you.
From now on,
they won't be messing
with you ever again.
How did you do that?
With my brainpower.
Everybody has desires.
I just fulfill them
to get what I want in return.
It's a win-win.
So, what does
she want?
Never mind.
You don't need to know everything.
Is it good that she stopped
messing with you?
Pa'Porn.
Please return to your cell.
It's getting late already.
Sure.
Let me guess...
The shoes are sold out?
Are you kidding me?
We've got a whole lot of them here.
Are you blind or what?
Yours is size 38, right?
How much?
Don't worry.
Just have to pay us back later.
Oh, thank you.
Bye!
Am I now sharing the room with you?
I'm sorry for entering
without telling you.
I just need a place to be alone.
Are you telling me to leave?
No, I'm not.
Come and join me.
Thanks for letting me in.
New shoes?
I lost the old pair.
That's why I had to get a new pair.
Here.
Write your name on them.
So, you can find out
who took them later.
I'd better put your name on these,
so nobody dares to steal them.
Suit yourself.
And...
What mood are you in,
sitting here all by yourself?
Exhausted? I guess?
I feel like I'm fighting by myself.
Fighting against what?
At first...
I was fighting for my freedom.
Now...
It's like I'm just fighting
to survive here.
You're not fighting alone, you know?
Everyone's fighting for the same thing.
To survive...
and get out of here.
What about you?
What are you fighting for?
I'm not fighting for anything.
I chose to stay here.
Life out there...
There's not much for me to hope for.
Perhaps,
I'm much happier living here.
Can I ask you something?
Why do you always help me?
I just hate seeing
someone get threatened.
That's all.
Or is it because you like me?
What kind of nonsense was that?
You want a piece of this?
Stop trying to scare me.
If you were going to hurt me,
you would've done it long ago.
Fine.
You don't have to answer me.
You remind me of myself
when I first got here.
How so?
I felt lost
in the dark.
I know
how bad you must've felt,
the overwhelming feeling,
and doubts, asking yourself,
"Why does it have to be me
who ends up here,
even though I did nothing wrong?
Why
do they have to leave me all alone?"
That makes me realize
how important it is
to have someone by our side.
So, back to my first question.
Do you like me?
How are things?
Feeling better?
Mm. I'm much better now.
Have a good rest, then.
Inmate Bell. Step outside.
Yes?
[Claire]
A visitor is coming to see you.
Right now?
Just move already.
I'll wait outside, okay?
Oh, Pa?
Hitting the hay already?
You haven't taken your meds yet.
Where did you put your meds?
Have a seat. Bell.
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry, Bell.
I had no choice.
My dad forced me to say those words.
It's fine, Top.
I'm down to break up.
If you're not helping me,
then I'll find a way out myself.
Bell, I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean to do that.
I've never wanted to break up with you...
- My dad...
- Stop talking.
I just want to know
why you stopped hiring Nurse Auay.
Pa.
Pa...
Pa'Porn!
Wake up, beautiful!
The reason I'm here is
to tell you this.
Stay calm, okay?
So...
Your dad has passed away.
Pa...
Pa!
Guards!
Help Pa, please!
Pa'Porn.
Pa'Porn...
Please come and help her!
We made our promise, didn't we?
Please keep our promise, Pa.